(Leslie:)They just wouldn't listen.
(Howard:)Well, we're surrounded.
(Howard:)So I guess there's nothing for us to do
but wait to be captured or killed.
Hm. That's the worst part.
(Leslie:)The waiting.
(Howard:)All the while knowing that there's a paint
pellet out there with your name on it.
(Howard:)Yeah.
(Leslie:)The big wet ball of death.
[PAINTBALLS SPRAYING SHED]
(Leslie:)Kind of makes you feel more alive,
doesn't it?
(Howard:)It kind of does.
(Leslie:)I say we make every moment count.
(Howard:)I agree.
(Howard:)How exactly do we do that?
[PAINTBALLS FIRING IN DISTANCE]
LEONARD:
Howard, why aren't you covering us?
(Leonard(voice):)We're getting slaughtered out here.
(Howard:)War is hell.